Milch Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Alphabetical Files, 1911-1962, Series 1:
  - Norton-Pittman (Reel 4427)
    Parshall, DeWitt
    Parshall, Douglass E.
    Pavlosky, Vladimir
    Paxton, Elizabeth O.
    Payne, Edgar A.
    Payne, Elsie P.
    Pearson, Ralph
    Perrine, Van Dearing
    Peterson, Jane
    Pickman, George
    Pittman, Hobson
  - Pittman-Reid (Reel 4428)
    Platt, Charles A.
    Pleissner, Ogden M.
    Plunder, Franz
    Pollak, Max
    Pollak-Ottendorf, Emil
    Pollet, Joseph
    Poore, Henry R.
    Poray, Stan
    Portnoff, Alexander
    Posfay, Oliver
    Postgate, Margaret
    Potter, William J.
    Poussette-Dart, Nathaniel
    Power-O'Malley, Michael A.
    Prellwitz, Henry
    Pregel, Alexandra
    Presnal, W. Boleslaw
    Prindeville, Mary
    Prophet, Mary Elizabeth
    Pugh, Mabel
    Quincy, Edmund
    Rader, Isaac
    Raleigh, Henry
    Ravelin, Grace
    Recchia, Richard
    Redfield, Edward W.
    Reich, Jacques
    Reid, Robert
  - Reid-San Francisco (Reel 4429)
    Reiss, Lionel S.
    Renne, O. A.
    Reynard, Grant [Tyson]
    Ricci, Jerri
    Ricci, Ulysses Anthony
    Richmond, Leonard
    Ritman, Louis
    Ritschel, William
    Robinson, Jay
    Robinson, Robert B.
    Roche, Marguerite
    Rogers, Charles B.
    Rohland, Caroline S.
    Romano, Umberto
    Rook, Edward F.
    Rose, Iver
    Rosenberg, H. M.
    Rosenblatt, Therese S.
    Rosenfeld, Lester
    Rosin, Harry
    Ribincam, Barclay
    Rungius, Carl
    Ryder, Chauncey F.
    Ryerson, Margery
    Saber, Clifford
    Salko, Samuel
    Sample, Paul
    Samstang, Gordon
    Sandleri, John
  - San Francisco-Sharp (Reel 4430)
    Saporita, John
    Saunders, Kendall
    Sawyer, Helen [Mrs. Jerry Farnsworth] (See also: Jerry Farnsworth)
    Sawyer, Wells M.
    Schille, Alice
    Schmitt, Carl
    Schreiber, Georges
    Schriener, Albert
    Schofield, W. Elmer
    Schuster, Will
    Schwacha, George, Jr.
    Schwarts, William
    Scott, Jeannette
    Scott, Jonathan
    Seltzer, Olaf C.
    Serra, Daniel
    Sexton, Leo Lloyd
    Shapiro, David
    Sharp, J. H.
    Sharp, John
  - Sharp-Stephenson (Reel 4431)
    Sheets, Millard O.
    Sheets, Nan
    Shepler, Dwight
    Sherry, William Grant
    Sherwood, Ruth
    Shokler, Harry
    Shope, Henry
    Shore, Henrietta
    Short, Jessie
    Simmons, William
    Sinclair, Gerrit V.
    Singer, William H.
    Sisti, Anthony
    Skou, Sigurd
    Smith, Albert D.
    Smith, Andre
    Smith, Georgine Wetherell
    Smith, Marshall D.
    Soderberg, Yngve E.
    Solomon, Mitzi
    Speicher, Eugener
    Speight, Francis
    Spencer, Robert
    Stafford, Charles
    Steadman, William E., Jr.
    Stebbins, Irene Boucher
    Steel, Kenneth
    Steene, William
  - Sterling-Union (Reel 4432)
    Sterne, Maurice
    Sterner, Albert
    Stevens, W. Lester
    Stinson, J. Whitla
    Strasser, Roland
    Strauss, Betty
    Sturtevant, Helena
    Swisher, Allan
    Symmers, Mrs. James K.
    Tanner, Henry O.
    Taylor, John
    Thayer, Abbott H.
    Thomas, Mrs. Vernon
    Thomas, Wilford
    Thompson, Frederick
    Thorne, Diana
    Thorne, William
    Thwaites, Charles W.
    Tolman, Robert
    Trebilcock, Paul
    Trubach, Ernest S.
    Tryon, Dwight W.
    Turner, Helen M.
    Tuttle, Macowin
    Twachtman, John H.
    Ufer, Walter
    Ullman, Eugene Paul
  - United-Weiss (Reel 4433)
    Usher, Leila
    Van Brunt, Gene
    Van Ryder, Jack
    Vance, James
    Varian, Dorothy
    Vincent, Harry A.
    Visson, Philip
    Volk, Douglas
    Vonnoh, Robert
    Woorhees, W. P.
    Walter, Martha
    Warneke, Heinz
    Warner, Everett
    Warren, Ferdinand
    Watkins, Franklin C.
    Watson, Jean
    Watt, Malcolm Rouse
    Watt, William G.
    Waugh, Frederick J.
    Wearstler, Albert M.
    Weber, Sybilla Mittell
    Webster, Clifford L.
    Weidner, Roswell
    Weir, J. Alden
    Weir, John F,
  - Weiss-Worcester Museum (Reel 4434)
    White, Henry C.
    White, Wade
    Whorf, John
    Wickey, Harry
    Wiegand, Gustave A.
    Wiggins, Carleton
    Wiggins, Guy
    Wilcox, Lois
    Wiles, Irving R.
    Wilford, Loran Frederick
    Wilkie, James
    Wilkinson, E. E.
    Willis, Robert
    Wingate, Carl
    Wingmouth, Stan
    Witkus, William
    Wood, Morton
    Woodward, Robert Strong
    Woodward, Stanley
    Woolf, Samuel Johnson
  - Worcester Museum-Z; Illegible and Unknown (Reel 4435)
    Wright, Alice Morgan
    Wright, Catherine Morris
    Wyeth, Andrew
    Zucker, Jacques
- Sales Records and Inventories, 1911-1969, undated, Series 2:
  Sales records consist of carbon copies of receipts, 1916-1929 (18 volumes); order forms, 1916-1968; sales registers, 1911-1931 (5 volumes); and card indices, 1918-1966 (5 files) recording paintings sold and returned, exhibited and consigned. Inventories of Milch Galleries stock, 1916-1967 (25 volumes) include some separate listings for specific categories such as prints, frames, and bronzes.
  The series is organized into two subseries:
  2.1: Sales Records, 1911-1969, undated
  2.2: Inventories of Milch Gallery Stock, 1916-1967
  - Sales Records, 1911-1969, undated, 2.1:
    Sales receipt and carbon copy volumes record the name and address of purchaser, description of merchandise (paintings, prints, frames) or service (framing, restoration, hanging or other labor), and price. Order forms duplicate information recorded in the sales records, but cover a longer time span and sometimes are more specific concerning titles and dimensions of works of art purchased; order numbers do not coincide with receipt numbers, and are cross referenced only in the receipt books.
    - Sales Receipts, Carbon Copies (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 1, #1001-#1996, Nov. 1916-Dec. 1917 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 2, #1997-#3016, April 1917-Feb. 1918 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 3, #1-#998, Jan. 1918-Dec. 1918 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 4, #901-#1908, Dec. 1918-Oct. 1919 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 5, #1909-#2916, July 1919-April 1920 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 6, #2917-#3909, April 1920-April 1921 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 7, #3910-#4902, April 1921-April 1922 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 8, #4912-#5913, April 1922-April 1923 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 9, #5950-#6948, May 1923-Dec. 1924 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 10, #6976-#8004, Nov. 1924-Jan. 1926 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 11, #8001-#9002, Jan. 1926-Feb. 1927 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 12, #9001-#10005, Feb. 1927-March 1928 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 13, #106-#1113, March 1928-June 1929 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 14, #1114-#2121, June 1929-Dec. 1930 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 15, #2122-#3126, Jan. 1930-Jan. 1934 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 16, #3129-#3575, March 1934-Oct. 1935 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 17, #3576-#4028, Oct. 1935-April 1937 (Reel unfilmed)
      - Volume 18, #4028-#4561, April 1937-May 1939 (Reel unfilmed)
    - Order forms, 1917-1918 (Reel 4436)
    - Order forms, 1918-1919 (Reel 4437)
    - Order forms, 1919-1921 (Reel 4438)
    - Order forms, 1921-1923 (Reel 4439)
    - Order forms, 1923-1925 (Reel 4440)
    - Order forms, 1925-1927 (Reel 4441)
    - Order forms, 1927-1929 (Reel 4442)
    - Order forms, 1929-1931 (Reel 4443)
    - Order forms, 1931-1937 (Reel 4444)
    - Order forms, 1937-1943 (Reel 4445)
    - Order forms, 1943-1950 (Reel 4446)
    - Order forms, 1950-1968 (Reel 4447, Frame 8-1504)
    - Sales register, April 1911-April 1913 (Reel 4447, Frame 1510-1590)
    - Sales register, frames made, April 1915-May 1916 (Reel 4447, Frame 1591-1630)
    - Sales register, 1918-1919 (Reel 4447, Frame 1631-1644)
    - Sales register A-Z, 1913-1931 (Reel 4448, Frame 6-466)
    - Sales register B-Z, 1916-1926 (Reel 4448, Frame 467-740)
    - Sales register B-Z, cont.1916-1926 (Reel 4449, Frame 9-604)
    - Paintings loaned for exhibition and returned, A-Z (card file), 1927-1960 (Reel 4449, Frame 606-854)
    - Paintings sold and returned (card file), A-C, 1956-1966 (Reel 4449, Frame 857-1474)
    - Paintings sold and returned (card file), C-R, 1956-1966 (Reel 4450)
    - Paintings sold and returned (card file), R-Z, 1956-1966 (Reel 4451, Frame 1-932)
    - Exhibition and consignment records A-Z (card file), 1918-1969 (Reel 4451, Frame 935-1855)
    - On consignment and exhibition A-J, 1919-1926 (Reel 4451, Frame 1858-1916)
    - On consignment and exhibition J-Z, 1919-1926 (Reel 4452, Frame 6-66)
    - Paintings and bronzes on consignment, 1919-1927 (Reel 4452, Frame 67-126)
    - Exhibitions A-Z, 1920-1928 (Reel 4452, Frame 127-170)
    - Receipts for pieces consigned, 1920-1954 (Reel 4452, Frame 172-675)
  - Inventories of Milch Gallery Stock, 1916-1967, 2.2:
    - "Record stock previous to June 1, 1924," 1924 (Reel 4452, Frame 680-779)
    - Prints, 1916-1928 (Reel 4452, Frame 780-858)
    - Loose prints, 1916-1959 (Reel 4452, Frame 859-957)
    - Frames, 1916-1939 (Reel 4452, Frame 958-970)
    - Framed prints and mirrors, 1917-1939 (Reel 4452, Frame 971-1096)
    - Pocket inventory (paintings), 1920s (Reel 4452, Frame 1097-1228)
    - Paintings, 1920s (Reel 4453, Frame 10-205)
    - Inventory, 1920s (Reel 4453, Frame 207-407)
    - Frames, paintings, and prints, 1920-1950 (Reel 4453, Frame 409-480)
    - Inventory, 1926-1967 (Reel 4453, Frame 481-527)
    - Inventory, 1927-1930 (Reel 4453, Frame 528-741)
    - Inventory, 1930s (Reel 4453, Frame 742-752)
    - Inventory, 1930s (Reel 4453, Frame 753-945)
    - Inventory, 1931-1944 (Reel 4453, Frame 946-1138)
    - Inventory, 1931-1960 (Reel 4453, Frame 1139-1205)
    - Inventory, 1931-1960 cont. (Reel 4454, Frame 8-257)
    - Inventory, 1951-1967 (Reel 4454, Frame 258-302)
    - Inventory, undated (Reel 4454, Frame 303-313)
    - Inventory, undated (Reel 4454, Frame 314-318)
    - Pocket inventory (paintings), undated (Reel 4454, Frame 319-419)
    - Record Book I: Bronzes, circa 1921-1922 (Reel 4454, Frame 420-465)
    - Record Book II: Bronzes, 1923-1924 (Reel 4454, Frame 466-510)
    - Record Book no. 3: Bronzes, 1925-1926 (Reel 4454, Frame 511-560)
    - Record Book III: Bronzes, 1925-1926 (Reel 4454, Frame 561-632)
    - Record Book IV: Bronzes, 1926-1927 (Reel 4454, Frame 633-746)
    - Record Book V: Bronzes, 1928-1929 (Reel 4454, Frame 747-826)
- Financial Records, 1914-1980, undated, Series 3:
  Included in the financial records found in this series are general ledgers, 1916-1969 (10 volumes), pay roll, 1914-1960 (2 volumes), cash books, 1915-1967 (20 volumes), and sales and purchases, 1916-1966 (5 volumes). Sales and purchase records are accounting records only, listing names of buyers but not titles (see Series II, Sales Records and Inventories for this information). Other financial records include individual and corporate tax returns, 1917-1980, filed by the Milches and E. & A. Milch, Inc. for federal and local taxes; unemployment and workmen's compensation; and social security tax receipts. Bills and receipts, 1927-1964, are for services and merchandise purchased by Milch Gallery, excluding works of art.
  - General ledgers, 1916-1969, (10 volumes) (Reel unfilmed)
  - Payroll, 1914-1960, (2 volumes) (Reel unfilmed)
  - Cash books, 1915-1967, (16 volumes) (Reel unfilmed)
  - Petty cash books, 1924-1943, (4 volumes) (Reel unfilmed)
  - Sales and purchases, 1916-1966, (5 volumes) (Reel unfilmed)
  - Taxes, 1917-1980, undated (Reel unfilmed)
  - Bills and receipts A-Z, 1927-1964 (Reel unfilmed)
- Printed Matter, 1886, 1910-1967, undated, Series 4:
  This series contains Milch Gallery exhibition catalogs, checklists, invitations, announcements, publications, and two scrapbooks. Many of the Milch Gallery exhibition catalogs and checklists are priced or otherwise annotated: see Appendix A for a full list of these. A complete run of Milch Gallery Art Notes is included here. One scrapbook contains clippings, catalogs, and invitations relating to early exhibitions held at the Edward Milch Galleries and E. & A. Milch, Inc., and artists represented by them. A second scrapbook contains a biographical sketch and clippings, about Thomas Moran.
  Sculpture files contain photographs, printed reproductions, and clippings. Publicity for solo exhibitions includes clippings, catalogs, invitations, and other printed matter relating to solo exhibitions held at the Milch Gallery.
  Christmas cards include original art by Norman Barr, Frank Di Gioia, Douglas Greenbowe, Harry Gottlieb, Luigi Lucioni, John Noble, and Thomas Mason, and reproductions from the collection of Dr. and Mrs. Walter Timme. Miscellaneous printed matter not from Milch Gallery includes a Catalogue of the Mrs. Mary J. Morgan Collection, 1886; Catalogue of the Charles M. Kurtz Collection, 1910; Artists Equity Association ball programs, 1950 and 1951; and a scrapbook of clippings about Walter Philipps, 1948. Publicity relating to group shows includes clippings, invitations, and catalogs.
  Sculpture files and publicity for solo exhibitions are arranged alphabetically by artist.
  - Scrapbook, 1912-1923 (Reel 4454, Frame 834-958)
  - Milch Galleries Exhibition Catalogs and Checklists, 1917-1929, undated (Reel 4454, Frame 960-1249)
  - Milch Galleries Exhibition Catalogs and Checklists, 1929-1967, undated (Reel 4455, Frame 8-1042)
  - Milch Galleries Art Notes, 1918-1928/29 (Reel 4455, Frame 1043-1215)
  - Clippings, 1921-1940, undated (Reel 4455, Frame 1219-1372)
  - Clippings, 1940-1956, undated (Reel 4456, Frame 9-153)
  - Sculpture files, A-Z and Unknown (Reel 4456, Frame 155-308)
  - Reproductions of works of art, A-Z (Reel 4456, Frame 310-349)
  - Publicity for solo exhibitions, A-Z, 1947-1966 (Reel 4456)
    - Alt, George (Reel 4456, Frame 350-358)
    - Blagden, Thomas (Reel 4456, Frame 359-405)
    - Bohrod, Aaron (Reel 4456, Frame 406-459)
    - Bostwick, Electra (Reel 4456, Frame 460-470)
    - Bosa, Louis (Reel 4456, Frame 471-499)
    - Connaway, Jay (Reel 4456, Frame 500-510)
    - Dehn, Adolf (Reel 4456, Frame 511-540)
    - Di Gioia, Frank (Reel 4456, Frame 541-582)
    - Di Valentin, Louis (Reel 4456, Frame 583-595)
    - Edmiston, Henry (Reel 4456, Frame 596-602)
    - Etnier, Stephen (Reel 4456, Frame 603-683)
    - Fransioli, Thomas (Reel 4456, Frame 709-718)
    - Fredenthal, David (Reel 4456, Frame 684-197)
    - Fromkes, Maurice (Reel 4456, Frame 698-718)
    - Gluckmann, Grigory (Reel 4456, Frame 719-771)
    - Gonzalez, Xavier (Reel 4456, Frame 772-198)
    - Greenbowe, Douglas (Reel 4456, Frame 799-817)
    - Greenwood, Marion (Reel 4456, Frame 818-825)
    - Hassam, Childe (Reel 4456, Frame 826-845)
    - Hayward, Mildred (Reel 4456, Frame 846-851)
    - James, Frederic (Reel 4456, Frame 852-858)
    - Kayn, Hilde (Reel 4456, Frame 859-881)
    - Koni, Nicolaus (Reel 4456, Frame 882-892)
    - Kopman, Benjamin (Reel 4456, Frame 894-898)
    - Kroll, Leon (Reel 4456, Frame 899-918)
    - Laufman, Sidney (Reel 4456, Frame 919-937)
    - Lawson, Ernest (Reel 4456, Frame 938-941)
    - Lutz, Dan (Reel 4456, Frame 942-968)
    - MacRae, Elmer (Reel 4456, Frame 969-977)
    - Martin, Fletcher (Reel 4456, Frame 978-987)
    - Mellon, Eleanor (Reel 4456, Frame 988-992)
    - Moreing, David Burr (Reel 4456, Frame 993-1008)
    - O'Hara, Elliot (Reel 4456, Frame 1009-1020)
    - Pleissner, Ogden (Reel 4456, Frame 1021-1069)
    - Philipp, Walter (Reel 4456, Frame 1070-1076)
    - Pittman, Hobson (Reel 4456, Frame 1077-1083)
    - Pregel, Alexandra (Reel 4456, Frame 1084-1105)
    - Ricci, Jerri (Reel 4456, Frame 1106-1131)
    - Ritman, Louis (Reel 4456, Frame 1132-1140)
    - Robinson, Jay (Reel 4456, Frame 1141-1169)
    - Rose, Iver (Reel 4456, Frame 1170-1176)
    - Sample, Paul (Reel 4456, Frame 1177-1196)
    - Samstang, Gordon (Reel 4456, Frame 1197-1202)
    - Schreiber, Georges (Reel 4456, Frame 1203-1215)
    - Shapiro, David (Reel 4456, Frame 1216-1239)
    - Sharp, John (Reel 4456, Frame 1240-1246)
    - Sterne, Maurice (Reel 4456, Frame 1247-1275)
    - Taylor, John (Reel 4456, Frame 1276-1306)
    - Tucker, Allen (Reel 4456, Frame 1307-1316)
    - Twachtman, John H. (Reel 4456, Frame 1317-1321)
    - Vance, James (Reel 4456, Frame 1322-1327)
    - Visson, Philip (Reel 4456, Frame 1328-1330)
    - Visson, Philip, cont. (Reel 4457, Frame 8-17)
    - Warren, Ferdinand (Reel 4457, Frame 18-24)
    - Whorf, John (Reel 4457, Frame 25-92)
    - Whorf, Richard (Reel 4457, Frame 93-101)
    - Zucker, Jacques (Reel 4457, Frame 102-120)
  - Publicity relating to group shows, 1947-1964 (Reel 4457, Frame 123-219)
  - Christmas cards (Reel Unfilmed)
  - Miscellaneous printed matter (not Milch Gallery) (Reel 4457, Frame 224-741)
- Photographs, 1903-circa 1944, undated, Series 5:
  This series primarily contains photographs of works of art. Also found are photographs of the Dodsworth Collection and a two volume album labelled "L. Ricci" containing photographs of antique furniture. There are a very small number of exterior and interior photographs of Milch Gallery as well as photographs of individuals, including some artists.
  Prints are first in the series, followed by negatives. Photographs of works of art are arranged alphabetically by name of artist, as are photographs of individuals.
  - Works of art, A-Z and unknown (Reel 4457, Frame 746-998)
  - Works of Art, A-Z and unknown, cont. (Reel 4458, Frame 9-48)
  - Dodsworth Collection (Reel 4458, Frame 49-84)
  - L. Ricci photo album of antique furniture, volume 1, 1920 (Reel 4458, Frame 86-176)
  - L. Ricci photo album of antique furniture, volume 2, 1920 (Reel 4458, Frame 177-260)
  - Milch Gallery exterior (Reel 4458, Frame 262-265)
  - Milch Gallery interior (Reel 4458, Frame 266-268)
  - People--Individuals, A-Z (Reel 4458)
    - Abbey, Edwin Austin (Reel 4458, Frame 271-273)
    - Bruce, Edward (Reel 4458, Frame 274-275)
    - Darley, Felix O. (Reel 4458, Frame 276-277)
    - Davies, Arthur B. (Reel 4458, Frame 278-279)
    - De Haven, Frank (Reel 4458, Frame 280-281)
    - Henry, E. L. (Reel 4458, Frame 282-283)
    - Lie, Jonas (Reel 4458, Frame 284-285)
    - Metcalf, Rosalind and Addison [children of Willard L. Metcalf] (Reel 4458, Frame 286)
    - Milch, Albert (Reel 4458, Frame 287-289)
    - Milch, Edward (Reel 4458, Frame 290-292)
    - Moran, Thomas (Reel 4458, Frame 293-295)
    - Murphy, J. Francis, 1919 (Reel 4458, Frame 296-298)
    - Noble, John (Reel 4458, Frame 299-300)
    - Twachtman, J.H., with students (Reel 4458, Frame 301-302)
    - Unidentified (Reel 4458, Frame 303-305)
  - People--groups: Ten American Artists; Associated Dealers in American Paintings, 1903, [circa 1944] (Reel 4458, Frame 306-312)
  - People--individuals A-Z (oversize): Thomas Moran (1915, 1918, 1924); Edward and Albert Milch; and unidentified, 1915-1924, undated (Reel 4458, Frame 316-330)
  - People--groups (oversize): dinner tendered to Bruce Crane by Samuel Shaw, Salmagundi Club, (1918); National Academy of Design Annual Dinner (1915); and two unidentified groups, 1915-1918, undated (Reel 4458, Frame 331-332, 369-374)
  - Works of art, A-Z and unknown (oversize) (Reel 4458, Frame 333-368)
  - Negatives of works of art, A-STE (Reel Unfilmed)
  - Negatives of works of art, Speight-Z, unifdentified, and works by more than one artist (Reel Unfilmed)
  - People--groups: Ten American Artists (1903); Milch Galleries interior (broken windows); and unidentified subjects, 1903, undated (Reel Unfilmed)
- Miscellaneous, 1916-1970, undated, Series 6:
  Miscellaneous records include legal documents, a certificate of membership in the Art Dealers Association, and package and shipping receipts. Due to mislabelling of some receipt books, the package receipt book for 1949-1952 was inserted between 1936 and 1937.
  - Membership certificate, Art Dealers Association, 1962 (Reel 4458, Frame 378-380)
  - Legal documents, 1917-1970 (Reel 4458, Frame 383-426)
  - Package receipts (loose), 1917-1949 (Reel 4458, Frame 428-1132)
  - Package receipts (loose), 1949-1968, undated (Reel 4459, Frame 6-1071)
  - Package receipts (bound), 1916-1917 (Reel 4459, Frame 1075-1568)
  - Package receipts, 1917-1920 (Reel 4460)
  - Package receipts, 1920-1923 (Reel 4461)
  - Package receipts, 1923-1928 (Reel 4462)
  - Package receipts, 1928-1932 (Reel 4463)
  - Package receipts, 1932-1955 (Reel 4464, Frame 1-925)
  - Shipping receipts (bound), collect (target incorrectly reads 1955-1963), 1955-1977 (Reel 4464, Frame 928-1068)
  - Shipping receipts (bound), prepaid, 1955-1965 (Reel 4464, Frame 1069-1236)
  - Shipping receipts (bound), prepaid, cont., 1955-1965 (Reel 4465)
Index: Milch Gallery Exhibition Lists and Checklists
Items marked with an asterisk (*) are contained in the scrapbook (Reel 4454, Frames 834-958) rather than with the Milch Gallery exhibition catalogs.
Date Exhibition
Nov. 16-Dec. 7, 1912* Exhibition of 300 Original Sketches in Oil by 100 Well Known American Artists
Feb. 15-March 8, 1913* Glimpses of Nature We Love to See, Feast, and Dwell On
April 28-May 7, 1913* Portraits of Children and Grown-Ups by Miss Susan Ricker Knox
Oct. 18-Nov. 1, 1913* Small Paintings and Bronzes
Oct. 18-Nov. 1, 1913* Exhibition of Paintings and Sculptures by Noted American Artists
Feb. 9-21, 1914* Paintings by W. Herbert Dunton of The Old West
Oct. 17-31, 1914* Portraits in Oil, Miniatures, and Sculpture
Feb. 20-March 7, 1915* Paintings and Etchings by Gordon Mallet McCouch
April 26-May 8, 1915* Paintings by Frew W. Kost, N.A.
Nov. 7-19, 1915 Paintings and Sculpture by Matilda Browne
Nov. 15-30, 1915* Views of the Panama California Exposition and Landscapes of Southern California
Jan. 31-Feb. 12, 1916 Paintings by Garber, Pearson, Lathrop, and Spencer
Feb. 14-26, 1916* Landscapes by Walter Clark, N.A.
Feb. 14-26, 1916* Paintings by Guy Wiggins
Nov. 4-18, 1916* Opening Exhibition
Nov. 25-Dec. 9, 1916* Works by the Late Louis Loeb
Jan. 15-27, 1917* Paintings by Helen M. Turner
Jan. 30-Feb. 10, 1917* Paintings by Leonard Ochtman, N.A.
Feb. 14-24, 1917* Recent Paintings by William V. Schevill
March 6-24, 1917 Ten American Painters
March 13-24, 1917* George Bellows
March 14-24, 1917* Paintings by Frederick J. Waugh
March 26-April 7, 1917* Paintings by Howard Russell Butler, N.A.
April 10-21, 1917 Paintings by Harry F. Waltman and Howard Giles, and Sculptures by Willard D. Paddock
April 15-27, 1917* Paintings by Valentino Molina
April 24-May 5, 1917* Paintings by Thalia Millet
Oct. 27-Nov. 17, 1917* William Jean Beauley
Jan. 15-Feb. 15, 1918* Etchings, Dry-Point and Lithographs by Ernest Haskell
Jan. 28-Feb. 4, 1918 Sketches and Paintings by the "Nova Scotia Group"
Feb. 25-March 16, 1918* Paintings by Robert Henri
March 13-24, 1918 George Bellows
March 22-April 4, 1918* Paintings by H. Gabrielle Levey
April 8-, 1918* Etchings by Allen Lewis
Nov. 25-Dec. 16, 1918* Paintings by Edward H. Potthast, N.A.
Dec. 18-Jan. 16, 1918 Annual Holiday Exhibition of Selected Paintings of Limited Size by American Artists
Dec. 23-Jan. 10, 1919* Etchings and Dry-Points by Ernest Haskell
Jan. 13-25, 1919* Paintings by Mary Prindeville
Jan. 27-Feb. 13, 1919* With the A.E.F., Paintings and Drawings Made at the Front by S. J. Woolf
Feb. 14-26 [1919?]* Paintings by Arthur C. Goodwin
Feb. 18-March 1, 1919* Paintings by Jerome Myers
March 3-16, 1919* Recent Paintings of California by William Ritschel, N.A.
March 17-29, 1919 Recent Paintings by Lillian Genth, A.N.A.
March 28-April 9, 1919* Drawings of New York City by Peter Marcus
April 8-30*, 1919 Paintings by Leading American Artists
April 19-May 1*, 1919 Paintings by Valentino Molina
May 3-22, 1919 Recent American Sculpture
May 5-17*, 1919 Recent American Sculpture in Bronze, Wood, and Terra Cotta for the Town and Country House, the Grounds, and Garden
May 20-, 1919 Flag Pictures and Street Scenes by Childe Hassam
Nov. 16-Dec. 6, 1919 Childe Hassam
Nov. 17-Dec. 6, 1919 Exhibition of Works in the Various Mediums by Childe Hassam